https://www.fishingholidayinspain.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyHomePrivacy Policy
Collection and Right to access of collected data
Information you provide prior to any registration process, such as your email when you provide it to us;
Information that you provide during any registration process, including in connection with a co-branded offer (such as your name, company name, email address, phone number, billing address or credit card information, geographic location and industry), when you call or email us (for support or otherwise) or when you use our products or services; and
Payment information that you provide to us (by way of our Services or otherwise) when you purchase some of our products and services, including credit card data.
You have the right to any of your personal data collected on this site and system and can ask for it by you completing this form here
How We Use Your Information
We have a legitimate interest in running a successful and efficient business and in providing you with Services and useful content, and we use the information we collect, both on its own and combined with any other information we collect about you, for the following purposes:
To provide the requested Services to you;
To provide you with useful content;
To ensure the proper functioning of our Services
To offer and improve our Services;
To provide you with requested information or technical support
To facilitate your movement through our websites or your use of our Services;
To do a better job of advertising and marketing our Services (our use of your information to do this is performed with your consent where required by applicable law);
In connection with our security and compliance programs;
To administer our websites;
To communicate with you;
To assist us in offering you a personalized experience or otherwise tailor our Services to you; and
As otherwise described in this privacy policy.
Payment information that you provide to us, including credit card data, will only be used to facilitate payment for our products and services.
Sharing of Information
We share personal information with other members of Nathan’s Charter Fishing to allow our corporate affiliates to contact you with offers, services or products that may be of interest to you and to provide you with their products and services. Any such corporate affiliate may use your information only according to the terms of this privacy policy. If you are located in a jurisdiction where such sharing requires your permission, we will only do so with your consent.
Right to be forgotten
You have the right to ask us to remove any of your personal data from our site and system in accordance with GDPR regulations, this can be done by you completing a request here
Menu
